(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Diego was going to the museum today.
It was the Museum of Natural History.
They had fossils there.
They had ancient artifacts.
He was most excited to see the dinosaur
fossils.
He went with his dad.
His dad took him to see many types
of animals.
He saw different types of dinosaurs.
He also saw mammals and birds.
He learned about their habitat.
He also learned the history of each animal.
He was fascinated.
Even his dad learned something.
After exploring the museum, his dad took him
to the gift shop.
Diego looked around.
He ended up buying some souvenirs.
He got a dinosaur keychain.
He would remember this day forever.